ALEXANDER E. DZIARNOWSKI

15089 Valhalla Court Haymarket, VA 20169 m: 703.226.9911 alexdziarn@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

To advance my career with a leading organization that will utilize my extensive cloud computing and FinTech knowledge while also allowing me to develop further as a professional

Proven talent for aligning business strategy and objectives with the intersection of financial analysis and efficient technological processes to achieve maximum operational impacts with minimum resource expenditures. Growth-focused thought leader with expertise spanning complex financial research, financial statement analysis, assessment of trends, markets and company performance, cloud computing, programming, Amazon Web Services, web security and project management. Exceptionally dedicated professional with keen interpersonal, communication, and organizational skills, as well as team leadership, policy compliance, and resource allocation expertise.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

AMPCUS INCORPORATED, CHANTILLY, VA, JUNE 2019 TO AUGUST 2019

FINANCE INTERN

- Played key role in business strategy development by exploring investment opportunities through the adept interviewing of prospective startup companies on the East Coast
- Gathered information related to customer financials, projected return, advantages in their industry, and company culture.
- Analyzed financial data in income statements and balance sheets using Microsoft Excel to evaluate company's past and current performances; developed trend analysis, projected results, and gave recommendations to the Ampcus President.
- Charted successful course for Socash (<u>www.socash.io</u>)
 - Generated financial analyses for a fast-growing Fintech app ranked in the top 10 of Google Play Singapore
 - Spearheaded development of a frontier analysis comparing the S&P 500 to all fintech stocks with an IPO in the past four years
 - Determined optimal points of investment for investors interested in Socash
 - o Facilitated financial and company information written in the initial draft of the SEC S-1 form

HIGHLIGHTED PROJECTS

CLOUD RESUME CHALLENGE, JULY 2020 TO PRESENT https://alexdziarnowski.com

CLOUD ENGINEER

- Designed a serverless web hosting website intended for large-scale and high-volume traffic
- Deployed code to AWS SAM, CloudFormation, and GitHub using Git commands
- Configured workflows (CI/CD) composed of Python unit testing and GitHub actions to automatically test and deploy code to my serverless architectures
- Streamlined process by incorporating open source tools, automation, and Cloud resources
- Ensured proper safeguards for user data by enabling encryption in transit (HTTPS) through Certificate Manager and CloudFront
- Produced a view counter to count web page visits using JavaScript, REST API, Lambda, and DynamoDB

Benny's Social Media, April 2020 to Present http://bennyfromblacksburg.com

CLOUD ENGINEER

- Orchestrated the creation of a web server running on Amazon Linux AMI EC2 instances
- Uploaded JPEG files to S3 and embedded the S3 file link in the web server's HTML
- Created a MySQL database through Amazon RDS and managed the database through MySQL Workbench
- Configured a text box and button to record user comments to the MySQL database
- Designed a text chat to gather and display user comments from the MySQL database
- Implemented the principle of least privilege by managing IAM security policies

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE (B.Sc.) IN FINANCE, 2020

Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University (Virginia Tech), Blacksburg, VA Concentration: Investment Management and CFA

COMPETITIONS

VIRGINIA TECH COUNTER-STRIKE TEAM, AUGUST 2016 TO MAY 2020

- Competed at a high level in more than 20 online and in-person competitions including Cstarleague, NACCS, and Corsair
- Led my team to a top-30 ranking in North America during my senior year

CYBERPATRIOT, DECEMBER 2015

- Cybersecurity competition run by The Air Force Association aimed at teaching advanced security principles
- Worked in teams of 4 to locate and remove security threats found within Windows and Linux operating systems

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Technical Proficiencies: AWS, Salesforce, Java, Microsoft Office, Excel Modeling, SQL, Python, Git, Web Programming

Certifications: Salesforce Administrator; Amazon Web Service Solutions Architect Associate; Amazon Web Service Developer Associate; Amazon Web Service SysOps Administrator Associate

Interests: Investing, Fantasy Sports, Gaming